Guide to the Records of the Office of the President (Oliva) RG.3.0.11
New York University Archives
- Series II. Writing and Speeches, 1963-2002; 21.2 Linear Feet in 48 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  - Subseries II.B Speeches, 1984-2002
    - Dinner for Lennart Philipson, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Caring Community Breakfast, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Classroom Naming Ceremony for Shimkin Hall, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Vittorio Gassman Dinner, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Presidential Lecture and Dinner for John Freccero, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Saturday at the Square Brunch, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Violet Ball, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - President's Service Awards Ceremony, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Reception in Honor of Dean Bob Berne (Wagner School), April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Samuel and May Rudin Urban Lecture Series, April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - 40th Anniversary of Brown v. Board of Education Conference -- "Brown + Forty", April 1994 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Reception in Honor of Middle States Association Self-Study Committee, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Library Symposium Welcome, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Silverstein Lounge and Study Center Dedication, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Women's Varsity Athletic Banquet, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Resource Network Schools' Visit, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - NYU Founders' Day, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Give a Violet Reception, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Middle States Association Dinner, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Kriser Family Dinner, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Higher Education Opportunity Program 25th Anniversary Celebration, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Athletic Achievement Awards, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Guidance Counselors Visit, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - 25-Year Service Awards Breakfast, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Service Recognition Reception, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Rudin Scholars Reception, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Prism Award Luncheon, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - NYU Community Fund Check Presentation, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - "The Holocaust in Southern Europe" Conference, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - School of Education Valedictory Ceremony, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - School of Continuing Education Class Day Exercises, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Stern School Pre-Commencement, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Salute to the Class of 1994, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Breakfast, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Commencement, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Medical School Last Day Exercises, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Alumni Council Awards Dinner, June 1994 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Vanderbilt Associates Reception for Martin Payson, June 1994 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Society of the Torch Luncheon, June 1994 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - School of Dentistry Graduation, June 1994 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - President's Council Reception, June 1994 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - "Rethinking Machiavelli" Conference, June 1994 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - News Conference Announcement of Global Law School, July 1994 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - C-Team Check Presentation, July 1994 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - President's Picnic, August 1994 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Americorps Reception Ceremony, September 1994 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Lasallian Conference, September 1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Memorial for Warren Dean, September 1994 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - School of Social Work Naming Dedication, September 1994 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Presentation of Irish Books to Ireland House, September 1994 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Gallatin Lecture with Shimon Peres, September 1994 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - New York Press Club Welcome, October 1994 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Governor's Senior Awards Ceremony, October 1994 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - American Council for Education (ACE)/National Association of Universities of Higher Education (ANUIES) Seminar and Breakfast, October 1994 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Marnold Fellows Roundtable with Former Mayors -- "A Forum on the Future of Our Cities", October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Dinner in Honor of College of Arts and Sciences Dean Matthew Santirocco, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Federation and Medallion Society Annual Dinner, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Americorps National Training Conference Convocation, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Reception in Honor of Tamar Schlick, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Associates Dinner, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars and Opportunity Fellows Reception, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - LaGuardia Statue Dedication, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Varsity Club Dinner, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Parents' Day President's Luncheon, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - New Faculty Reception, October 1994 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Sixth Annual HIV/AIDS Update Conference, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Irving H. Jurow Lecture Hall Naming, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Memorial Service for Hugo Castello, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Dr. James Hester Wing Dedication in Bobst Library, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Macarthur Fellows Reception, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Chemistry Department Celebration of Achievements, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame Induction and Awards Ceremony, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Morning at Washington Square, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Jerome Lemelson Luncheon, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Americorps Reception, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Bobst Library 20th Anniversary Dinner, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Fifth Annual La Herencia Latina Awards, November 1994 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Guidance Counselors' Reception, December 1994 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Morgan Stanley Scholars Breakfast, December 1994 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Henry Taub Dinner, December 1994 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Reception Honoring Stern School Donors and Presentation of the Richard L. Rosenthal Award, December 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Celebration for Dolores Briante, December 1994 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Washington University in St. Louis Alumni Reception, January 1995 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - University of Chicago Alumni Reception, January 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Views on the News: The Chet Huntley Memorial Lectures Luncheon, January 1995 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - University of Rochester Alumni Reception, January 1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Alumni Reception, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Emory University Alumni Reception, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Phil Furmanski Dinner, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Brandeis University Alumni Reception and Basketball Game, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Reception for New Humanities Chairs, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Torch of Learning Awards, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Gallatin School Gala, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - International Rector's Conference Group Dinner, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - George Soros Dinner, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - NYU Day in Albany Alumni Reception, February 1995 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 1995 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Duncan Rice Dinner, March 1995 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - School of Law Conference on Global Trade, Competition, and the Environment, March 1995 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Urban Leadership Award Diner, March 1995 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Billion Dollar Campaign Celebration and Gala, March 1995 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Roberto Goizueta Dinner, March 1995 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Saturday at the Square, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - President's Service Awards, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Senior Scholars Reception, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - National Scholars Competitions Reception, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Tom Bishop's 25th Anniversary Reception, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Founders' Day, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Hillary Rodham Clinton Lecture and Dinner, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - New York Foundling Hospital Anniversary, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Kriser Famiy Dinner, April 1995 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Guidance Counselors' Luncheon, May 1995 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - School of Education Valedictory Ceremony, May 1995 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - School of Social Work Salute to the Class of 1995, May 1995 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Salute to the Class of 1995, May 1995 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Commencement, May 1995 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - International Conference on Hunger and Visit of President of Ireland, Mary Robertson, May 1995 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Resource Network Reception, June 1995 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Council Awards Dinner, June 1995 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Prism Award Luncheon, June 1995 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Dinner Honoring Lieutenant Governor Betsy McCaughey, June 1995 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Investors in Excellence Luncheon, June 1995 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - President's Council Reception, June 1995 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Seward Park High School Graduation, June 1995 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Dinner Honoring Elizabeth Schlesinger, July 1995 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - All University Picnic, August 1995 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - New Faculty Introduction, September 1995 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Science Council Reception, September 1995 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars and Opportunity Fellows Reception, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Acton Scholars Reception, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Varsity Club Hall of Fame Dinner, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Gallatin Convocation and Dinner, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Americorps Project SafetyNet Panel, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Parents' Day Presidential Luncheon, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Convocation for Kim Young Sam, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - New Faculty Reception, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Visit by U.S. Secretary of Education Richard Riley, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - School of Social Work Benefit Dinner, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Federation and Medallion Society Annual Dinner, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Reception for Opening of the Institute of Afro-American Affairs and the Africana Studies Program, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Dinner Honoring Professor David Schwartz, October 1995 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Dinner Honoring Vice Deans Choi, Ghosh, and Pugel, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Tenth Annual Finance Forum, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - President's Meet the Press Dinner, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - NYU Alumni Association of New Jersey, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Musical Theater Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Dedication and Dinner for the Onassis Board, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Morning at Washington Square, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Dedication of Dan Quilty Room, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Resource Network Reception, November 1995 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Johns Hopkins University Alumni Basketball Reception, December 1995 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - School of Social Work Alumni Association Dinner for Eleanore Z. Korman, December 1995 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - President's Holiday Party for Students and Washington Square Windows Awards, December 1995 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Emory University Alumni Basketball Reception, January 1996 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - "The Role of Faculty Scholarship in the Teaching-Learning Process" Symposium, January 1996 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Dinner Honoring Eleanore Korman, January 1996 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Rochester University Alumni Basketball Reception, January 1996 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Rose-Marie Lewent Lounge Dedication, January 1996 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Walter Mosley Reception and Panel Discussion, February 1996 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - NYU Alumni in Florida, Planned Giving Seminar, February 1996 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Reception for Chancellor Rudolph Crew, New York City Board of Education, February 1996 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Stop-By Community Service Council Reception, February 1996 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Washington University in St. Louis Alumni Basketball Reception, February 1996 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - University of Chicago Alumni Basketball Reception, February 1996 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Dinner Honoring Thomas Meenaghan, February 1996 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Dinner Honoring Walter Mosley, February 1996 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - NYU in Albany Day Reception, February 1996 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Evening at Washington Square with Walter Mosley, February 1996 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 1996 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Evening at Washington Square with Wendy Wasserstein, March 1996 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - 1996 Torch of Learning Award Luncheon, March 1996 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Dinner Honoring Lonnie Bristow, President of the American Medical Association, March 1996 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Urban Leadership Award Dinner, Real Estate Institute, March 1996 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Science Council Lecture by Ken Perlin, March 1996 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - National Scholarship Finalist Reception, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - President's Service Awards, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Dinner Honoring Robert Bishop, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Dinner Honoring Seamus Heaney, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Retirement Reception for Larry Bornstein, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Dinner Honoring Kevin Brine, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - 25-Year Service Awards Breakfast, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Kriser Family Dinner, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Service Recognition Reception, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Chase Not-For-Profit Forum, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Founders' Day, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Protection Services Awards, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Senior Scholars Reception, April 1996 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Caring Community Breakfast, April 1996 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - "Classroom and the Community" -- Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México, April 1996 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Give A Violet Award Ceremony, April 1996 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - ABFAS Luncheon and Award Ceremony, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Dinner Honoring Giovanni Agnelli, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Chubb Awards Breakfast, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Silicon Alley Luncheon, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - NYU Community Fund Award Ceremony, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Pless Hall Dedication, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Stern Haskins Partners Dinner, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - School of Education Valedictory Celebration, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - School of Social Work Salute to Class of 1996, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - School of Continuing Education Class Day Exercises, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Stern School Undergraduate Pre-Commencement, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - College of Arts and Sciences Baccalaureate Ceremony, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Commencement, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Commencement Anniversary Alumni Reception, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - School of Medicine Last Day Exercises, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - School of Law Convocation, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Institute of International Education Breakfast Lecture, May 1996 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - School of Continuing Education Hospitality Industry Investment Conference Luncheon, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - School of Dentistry Graduation, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - New York Police Department Internal Affairs Nationwide Conference, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - President's Council Reception, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Convocation and Dinner for King Hussein of Jordan, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Chase/NYU Not-for-Profit Conference, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Institute of Afro-American Affairs End of Year Dinner, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Dinner for Duncan Rice, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Alumni Association Inaugural Awards Dinner, June 1996 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - President's Picnic, August 1996 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Council Reception, September 1996 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - New Faculty Introduction, September 1996 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - School of Continuing Education Training Program for New Diplomats, September 1996 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Ferragamo Reception, September 1996 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Villa La Pietra Dinner, September 1996 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - C-Team Orientation, September 1996 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Founders Society Dinner Cruise, September 1996 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - School of Social Work Conference -- "Systems in Transition: The Impact on the Latino Community of the Transition to a System of Medicaid Managed Behavioral Health Care", October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Guerlain Champs-Elysées Launch, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Dinner Honoring Boris Jordan, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - School of Continuing Education 42nd Street Building Dedication, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - School of Continuing Education Dinner Honoring Preston Robert Tisch, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars and Opportunity Fellows Presidential Reception, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Dinner for Earl Mack, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Kimball Commons Dedication, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Varsity Club Hall of Fame Dinner, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Irving H. Jurow Lecture, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - New York State Community College Presidential Summit, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Parents' Day, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - McCracken Fellowship Reception, October 1996 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - School of Continuing Education Sloan Press Conference to Announce Global Village College, November 1996 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Albert Gallatin Reception, November 1996 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - City Club of New York Luncheon, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Nicholas Wahl Memorial Service, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Finance Forum, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - A Morning at Washington Square, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame Dinner, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Reception in Honor of Joan Connelly, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Fulbright Program 50th Anniversary, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Acton Society Dinner, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Guidance Counselor Reception, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Reception for New Incumbents of Named Professorships in Faculty of Arts and Sciences, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Resource Network Reception for Liaison Officers, November 1996 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Case Western University Alumni Basketball Reception, December 1996 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Hartford Foundation Dinner, December 1996 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Bronfman Center for Jewish Student Life Dedication, December 1996 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Holiday Party for Student Leaders, December 1996 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - All University Holiday Sing, December 1996 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - NYU Medical Center Benefit Honoring E. John Rosenwald, Jr., December 1996 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Full Faculty Council Luncheon, December 1996 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Induction Dinner for Law School Trustees, January 1997 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - University of Chicago Alumni Reception, January 1997 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - American Jewish Congress Stephen S. Wise Award Dinner, January 1997 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - D. Kenneth Patton Reception, January 1997 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Acton Scholars Reception, January 1997 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Hemmerdinger Hall Dedication, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Emory University UAA Alumni Reception, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Carnegie Mellon University UAA Alumni Reception, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - President's Media Dinner, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Italian-American Student Club Reception, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - University of Rochester UAA Alumni Reception, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Achievement Award Dinner for Arthur Gelb, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Reception Honoring Duncan Rice, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Rectors' Conference, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - NYU in Albany Day Alumni Reception, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Gallatin 25th Anniversary Gala, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Event, Palm Beach, February 1997 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Brandeis University UAA Alumni Reception, March 1997 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Reading and Reception for Walter Mosley, March 1997 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Stern School Symposium Luncheon, March 1997 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 1997 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, March 1997 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Guggenheim Fellows Reception, March 1997 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Senator Jack Reed Luncheon, March 1997 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Mayor Giuliani's Visit with the NYU Women's Basketball Team, March 1997 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Borough President Ruth Messinger Proclamation Event with Women's Basketball Team, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Jesuit High School College Counselors Reception, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Saturday at the Square, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - President's Service Awards, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - King Juan Carlos I of Spain Visit, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Kriser Family Dinner, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - City Council and Women's Basketball Team Event, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Presidential Lecture with Joan Connelly, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Gruppo Esponenti Italiani (Group of Italian Representatives) Luncheon, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - School of Continuing Education's General Studies Program 25th Anniversary, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Athletic Academic Achievement Awards Reception, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Founders Day, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Luncheon for the Mayor of Moscow, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Senior Reception, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - National Scholarship Finalists Reception, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - University-Wide Day of Service Reception, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Chubb Scholarship/Internship Awards Breakfast, April 1997 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - 25 Year Service Awards Breakfast, May 1997 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Association of Black Faculty, Administrators and Staff Annual Awards Luncheon, May 1997 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Service Recognition Reception, May 1997 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - College Counselors Workshop, May 1997 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Protection Awards Ceremony, May 1997 (Box 53, Folder 23)